* Shop
    
    ### Shop by service
    
    * 
        
        #### Ancestry Service
        
        The most comprehensive ancestry breakdown on the market.

    * 
        
        #### Health +plus Ancestry Service
        
        Everything in Ancestry Service, plus a more complete picture of your health with insights from your genetic data.

    * 
        
        #### 23andMe  
        Premium™
        
        Everything in Health +plus Ancestry, plus access to new premium reports and features throughout the year.
        
        [Learn more about 23andMe  
        Premium™](https://www.23andme.com/membership/)
        
    * 
        
        #### 23andMe  
        Total Health™
        
        Everything in 23andMe+plus Premium, plus exome sequencing, biannual blood testing and genetics-informed clinical care.
        
        [Learn more about 23andMe  
        Total Health™](https://www.23andme.com/total-health/)

    ### Shop by interest

Open Menu

Close

* Shop
    
    ### Shop by service
    
    * 

        The most comprehensive ancestry breakdown on the market.
        
    * 

        Everything in Ancestry Service, plus a more complete picture of your health with insights from your genetic data.
        
    * 

        [23andMe  
        Premium™](https://www.23andme.com/membership/)
        
        Everything in Health +plus Ancestry, plus access to new premium reports and features throughout the year.

    ### Shop by interest

What you should know about privacy at 23andMe
=============================================

At 23andMe, Privacy is in our DNA.

This Privacy Statement applies to all websites owned and operated by 23andMe, Inc., including [www.23andme.com](https://www.23andme.com/), and any other websites, pages, features, or content we own or operate, and to your use of the 23andMe mobile app and any related Services. Should you choose to receive Telehealth Services coordinated through 23andMe, with clinical services provided through licensed healthcare providers, there is a separate [Medical Record Privacy Notice](https://www.23andme.com/legal/medical-record-privacy-notice/) that describes how your medical information is used, disclosed, and maintained.

To keep things simple, we use the same terms here as in our [Terms of Service](https://www.23andme.com/legal/terms-of-service/). We’ll let you know in this Privacy Statement if we have a new or different definition for a term. You should read our entire Privacy Statement, but if you only have a few minutes you can take a look at this [privacy summary](https://www.23andme.com/privacy/).

Once you submit your sample...

Here are the privacy choices you have along the way
---------------------------------------------------

Previous

### Account  
deletion

You can delete your 23andMe account any time. If you do, we will automatically opt you out of Research and discard your sample. Keep in mind this process cannot be cancelled or reversed.

### 2-Factor  
Authentication

You create your online account and password. Your account is protected with 2-factor authentication.

### Storing your  
sample

You can choose to have your sample stored. If not, no problem. It will be securely destroyed after the laboratory completes its work. Note that a discard choice cannot be reversed.

### Sharing  
features

You decide whether you want to participate in our sharing features, like DNA Relatives and Your Connections.

### Participate in  
Research

If you choose to participate in research, your deidentified data will be pooled with data from other participants. You can opt out at any time.

### Account  
deletion

You can delete your 23andMe account any time. If you do, we will automatically opt you out of Research and discard your sample. Keep in mind this process cannot be cancelled or reversed.

### 2-Factor  
Authentication

You create your online account and password. Your account is protected with 2-factor authentication.

### Storing your  
sample

You can choose to have your sample stored. If not, no problem. It will be securely destroyed after the laboratory completes its work. Note that a discard choice cannot be reversed.

### Sharing  
features

You decide whether you want to participate in our sharing features, like DNA Relatives and Your Connections.

### Participate in  
Research

If you choose to participate in research, your deidentified data will be pooled with data from other participants. You can opt out at any time.

### Account  
deletion

You can delete your 23andMe account any time. If you do, we will automatically opt you out of Research and discard your sample. Keep in mind this process cannot be cancelled or reversed.

Next

Quick links
-----------

Contact
-------

If you have questions about this Privacy Statement, or have a complaint or inquiry, please email 23andMe's Privacy Administrator at privacy@23andme.com, call us at 1.800.239.5230, or send a letter to:

Privacy Administrator  
23andMe, Inc.  
349 Oyster Point Blvd  
South San Francisco, CA 94080

Next Page: Information we collect

Last Updated: October 4, 2023.  

Footer
------

### Services

### Company

### Learn

### Legal

### Partner With Us

### Download App

United States | Change

### Change location

### Connect

© 2024 23andMe, Inc. All rights reserved.
